<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>[TP]Walkie-Talkie (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.TPWalkieTalkie</packageId>
  <author>TrahsPanda</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/TPWalkieTalkie</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of TrahsPandas mod https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2424065656

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr][td][url=https://dsc.gg/mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td] [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/TPWalkieTalkie][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/h5VwTNL.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
[spoiler]Hey bud, just wanted to plop this here to ask if you can leave a like on this mod? This mod is something I'll be using in my playthroughs from now on, so a like would be cool. Favorite if you want, I don't mind too much about those. :)[/spoiler]

[h1]DESCRIPTION[/h1]

The Walkie-Talkie is a pre-microelectronics Comms. Console and Orbital Trade Beacon. It requires only 5W of power, costs 40 steel and 1 component to make, and of course, can be placed indoors. Requires Electricity to be researched.

[h1]KNOWN ISSUES[/h1]
The trade radius is a rough 3 cell area around the Walkie Talkie, but when highlighted or placing it still shows a normal Orbital Trade Beacon's trade radius, being around 7 cells.

Currently incompatible with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2071695947]RimBank[/url]

[h1]LOAD ORDER[/h1]
Not really sure, but, I think you want to put this mod as close to core as you possibly can. Above Deep Storage and addons at the least.

[h1]CREDITS[/h1]

Thank you to iforgotmysocks for doing the C# code, send him love.
Thank you to YouHaveIt for suggesting the mod idea.

Bored? Wanna suggest a mod idea? Join my [url=https://discord.gg/m9K7rWp]Discord.[/url] I'm kinda on a mod rampage right now, so best to put your ideas in now.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] or the standalone [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Uploader[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/3023778210]Last updated 2023-08-23[/url]</description>
</ModMetaData>